{
    "id": "40236e841a1c48778b184f0f3157a821",
    "title": "Such And Such A",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "You talk …………….. nonsense.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "such",
                "such a"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "22848760b9a74a2da08e02d0bacd00a8"
        },
        {
            "question": "It took ………………….. long time to finish the job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "such",
                "such a"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5264536cb9bf42fe8cec3b1a31cdd141"
        },
        {
            "question": "I had ………………… difficulty finding accommodation in Beijing.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "such",
                "such a"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ed9aaf67b94f4c4196721945a1501dc6"
        },
        {
            "question": "You are ……………….. fool.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "such",
                "such a"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5e65601c95d04f9582d3537c0179dda5"
        },
        {
            "question": "It was ……………….. difficult test that I couldn’t answer most of the questions.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "such",
                "such a"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c9e34ab86f724ae18cc4e1f046a090ee"
        },
        {
            "question": "We are having ……………….. terrible weather at the moment.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "such",
                "such a"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ef2465805784458e85f922f21b1b2990"
        },
        {
            "question": "I won’t agree with any ……………. plan.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "such",
                "such a"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5798c38a31724af4a1e776f8cf9ab9b6"
        },
        {
            "question": "I won’t agree with ………………. plan.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "such",
                "such a"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4931362fc10344d98e6620e9dd8046ee"
        },
        {
            "question": "I had ……………… terrible experience yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "such",
                "such a"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0e61f91046ea47a5af2ee7fc2c780f8b"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is ………………… lovely girl.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "such",
                "such a"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "91478cc789b04606900cc10038163dd6"
        }
    ]
}